<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	  xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://apps.nextcloud.com/schema/apps/info.xsd">
	<id>safe_html_viewer</id>
	<name>Safe HTML Viewer</name>
	<summary>Preview HTML files safely with CSP sandbox and best-effort secret redaction</summary>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>Adds a <strong>"Safe HTML preview"</strong> file action to <code>.html</code> / <code>text/html</code> files. The file opens in a new tab served under a strict <code>Content-Security-Policy: sandbox allow-scripts allow-popups</code> — deliberately <strong>without</strong> <code>allow-same-origin</code> — so embedded JavaScript can run (charts, animations, interactive reports) while staying fully isolated from your Nextcloud session, cookies, DOM and same-origin APIs.</p>
			<p><strong>Features</strong></p>
			<ul>
				<li>One-click sandboxed preview of HTML files right from the Files app</li>
				<li>Respects Nextcloud permissions: only files visible to the logged-in user can be previewed</li>
				<li>Best-effort display-time redaction of secrets: email addresses, phone-like strings, IPv4 addresses, private/localhost URLs, and credential-like strings (<code>password=</code>, <code>token=</code>, <code>api_key=</code>, long opaque tokens)</li>
				<li>The original file is never modified — redaction only affects the served preview</li>
				<li>No external services, no telemetry; everything runs inside your Nextcloud</li>
			</ul>
			<p><strong>Limitations</strong>: redaction is best-effort pattern matching, intended to reduce accidental secret leakage when sharing HTML documents. It is not a DLP solution and comes with no leak-prevention guarantee — see SECURITY.md in the repository.</p>
		]]>
	</description>
	<version>0.1.1</version>
	<licence>agpl</licence>
	<author mail="ishizakahiroshi.dev@gmail.com" homepage="https://github.com/ishizakahiroshi">Hiroshi Ishizaka</author>
	<namespace>SafeHtmlViewer</namespace>
	<category>files</category>
	<bugs>https://github.com/ishizakahiroshi/nextcloud-safe-html-viewer/issues</bugs>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ishizakahiroshi/nextcloud-safe-html-viewer/main/screenshots/screenshot1.png</screenshot>
	<screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/ishizakahiroshi/nextcloud-safe-html-viewer/main/screenshots/screenshot2.png</screenshot>
	<dependencies>
		<nextcloud min-version="28" max-version="33"/>
	</dependencies>
</info>
